Fill
the
void
in
me
See life beyond the veil
Replace
all
thoughts
from
the
abyss
With cosmic energy
Ignite
the
flame
in
thee
Fill out the tree of your life
We are rooted deep in the darkness
We
are
rooted
deep
in
the
darkness
And keep growing towards the light
And
keep
growing
towards
the
light
Be without your fears
For a thousand years
Search for stillness deep inside
One thought that grows in the abyss of time
Fills up the vast space with matter and life
Free of the darkness that fetters the soul
Find at the source the end of your goal
Find
the
spark
in
me
See life beyond the dream
Replace
your
darkest
emotions
With pure divinity
Ignite
the
flame
in
me
Unite with your inner light
We should free ourselves from the shadows
We
should
free
ourselves
from
the
shadows
And the bondage of the night
And
the
bondage
of
the
night
Be without your fears
For a thousand years
Be the master of your life
One thought that grows in the abyss of time
Fills up the vast space with matter and life
Free of the darkness that fetters the soul
Find at the source the end of your goal
Fight back your fears forever
Be the master of your life
Learn to unlearn
In the beginning
There was a timeless, space-less, nothingness
And into that nothingness came a thought
Purposeful, all-pervading
So ended
The Void
Surge
the
Demiurge
Shaper
of
a
false
universe
Search
that
deadly
urge
Your
walls
of
self
protection
are
Walls of self-imprisonment
Walls
of
self
im
pri
son
ment
Be without your fears
For a thousand years
Search for stillness deep inside
Strive for harmony in duality
To revise the book of life
There was one thought that grew in the abyss of time
It filled up the vast space with matter and life
Freed from the darkness that fettered the soul
We found at the end our reason, our goal
We march on
We're counting down
To singularity
While we drown
We're moving on
To master wisdom
To
master
wisdom
To be free
To
be
free