!retime("syl",math.floor((j-1)*(0.05*syl.duration)),-math.floor((maxj-j)*(0.05*syl.duration)))!
!retime("line",0,-300)!
Fill the void in me
See life beyond the veil
Replace all thoughts from the abyss
With cosmic energy
Ignite the flame in thee
Fill out the tree of your life
We are rooted deep in the darkness
And keep growing towards the light
Be without your fears
For a thousand years
Search for stillness deep inside
One thought that grows in the abyss of time
Fills up the vast space with matter and life
Free of the darkness that fetters the soul
Find at the source the end of your goal
Find the spark in me
See life beyond the dream
Replace your darkest emotions
With pure divinity
Ignite the flame in me
Unite with your inner light
We should free ourselves from the shadows
And the bondage of the night
Be without your fears
For a thousand years
Be the master of your life
One thought that grows in the abyss of time
Fills up the vast space with matter and life
Free of the darkness that fetters the soul
Find at the source the end of your goal
Fight back your fears forever
Be the master of your life
Learn to unlearn
In the beginning there was a timeless, space-less, nothingness
And into that nothingness came a thought
purposeful, all-pervading. So ended the Void
Surge the Demiurge
Shaper of a false universe
Search that deadly urge
Your walls of self protection are
Walls of self-imprisonment
Be without your fears
For a thousand years
Search for stillness deep inside
Strive for harmony in duality
To revise the book of life
There was one thought that grew in the abyss of time
It filled up the vast space with matter and life
Freed from the darkness that fettered the soul
We found at the end our reason, our goal
We march on
We're counting down
To singularity
While we drown
We're moving on
To master wisdom
To be free