To
Be
Di
vine
LIVE IN
THIS
MOMENT
LIKE
THERE
IS NOT
PAST
ALL THAT
MATTER IS
TO
BE IN
THIS
MOMENT
JUDGMENTS
WILL NOT
LAST
URGE
YOURSELF
AGAIN
TO
TAKE
A LEAP
INTO
THE
DARE TO
THE POINT
OF NO
RETURN
RESTRAINS US
SHAKE OFF
OILED
FEATHERS
LEAVE
YOUR
PAST
BEHIND
USE YOUR
INNER FORCE
TO
WHEN
THERE'S
NO
FUTURE
YOU CAN'T
BE OCCUPIED
BY
NON-ESSENTIAL
WASTE
AND
RECREATE
DARE TO
THE POINT
OF NO
RETURN
RESTRAINS US
Someday you'll open up again
To learn and grow
Someday you'll have to reach for new endeavors
To perceive your inner self
Perceive your soul
Someday you'll start to live your life
Responding
with
is
a
small
lie
for
a man
but
a
giant
blow
for
mankind
we
have
found
the alchemy
of
life
we
are
the
force
in
control